Finding Aid for the Photographers' Collection LSC.0098
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Shelflist
  - Fleckenstein, Louis ***, 244 items. Photographs.
    - Medium images, chiefly 20 x 24 cm. 112 items.
      - "Feeding Time.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Girl and boy digging sand at bank of rover. (Box 2)
      - "The South Wind.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman with square white collar and hat with turned-up brim. (Box 2)
      - "After the Plunge.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Barefoot man with long hair, hands outstretched. (Box 2)
      - "Topanga Canyon.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Sunlit Pool.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
        Exhibited: Blanchard Hall Art Gallery, Los Angeles, undated.
      - "Saddle Trip to Half-Dome.", Signed on mount beneath image. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Nude with back to camera, hands above head. (Box 2)
      - "Song Bird of the Neills." (Posed by Beth Beri.), Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Eleanor.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "The Baby.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Earthquake Ruins.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "A Disciple of Satan.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "The San Antonio River.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Earthquake Refugees.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Ruins of Pusasima Concepcion.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Summit Ridge of Telescope Peak--Death Valley.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Cahuilla Indian.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Louis Fleckenstein (at work)." (Box 2)
      - "Departure from San Fong.", Signed and identified as Ruth Comfort Mitchell. (Box 2)
      - "Charlotte Remington in Indian Character Portrayal.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "San Francisco (0ne-Man Show by Louis Fleckenstein.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Portrait--F.S.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
        Exhibited: The London Salon of Photography, 1931; IX Salon Internacional de Fotografia, Madrid, 1932.
      - "L.F. on Telescope Peak." (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Portrait of Louis Fleckenstein. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Carl Rau. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Charles Lummis. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Louis Fleckenstein--Self portrait. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Florence (Box 2)
        Published in Photograms.
      - [Untitled.] Louis Fleckenstein, seated, with photographs for exhibitions., Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Devil's Slide. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Torrey Pine. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Ruth Comfort Mitchell. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Carl Rau, photographer, founder of Salon Club. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Golden Canyon, Death Valley. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Grove of trees. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman with long, curly hair, netting across shoulders. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Ruins? Willow tree in foreground. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Group viewing photographs. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Mountain scene. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman with bared left shoulder. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman and small boy. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in v-neck blouse looking upward. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young girl in light-colored hat. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Flowers in a field. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Man with moustache and light-colored straw hat. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Man and woman on steps outside a cabin. (Box 2)
      - "Over the Hill to the Poorhouse.", Gum print. (Box 2)
        On permanent loan to the Grunwald Center for the Graphic Arts.
      - "City of the Dead." (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman in pearl necklace. (Box 2)
      - "Marie.", Signed. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Grove of trees, mountain in background. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Charles Lummis. (Box 2)
  - Forrest, Ruth Roark, 4 items. Photographs. (Box 60)
  - Frasher, Burton, 21 items. Photographs.
    - Echo Park, 1941; B2873
    - Los Angeles from City Hall, 1940 March 9; B9611
    - Murray Canyon, 1931 March 1; F3511
    - Victor Hugo - Laguna Beach, 1948 March 18; E4219
    - River Lodge Lake - Parker Dam, 1949; E4577
    - Eaten's Restaurant - Santa Barbara, 1947 August 22; W1121
    - De La Guerre St. - Santa Barbara, 1947 August 22; W1122
    - Radio Kist, De La Guerre St. - Santa Barbara, 1947 August 22; W1126
    - La Plaza - Palm Springs, ca. 1944-1946; F3446
    - Santa Barbara Mission, ca. 1947; F4704
    - Mt. Wilson Observatory, 1947 January-February; F4200
    - Tom Brememon's Radio Program - Breakfast in Hollywood, 1947 March 22; F4260
    - Graumen's Chinese..., 1947 March 22; F4261
    - Entrance to the Desert Inn--Palm Springs, 1946; F6207
    - Palm Canyon, 1946; F6214
    - Dam Green Valley Lake, California, 1946; F6740
    - Mission San Luis Rey, 1948 June 18; F7597
    - Highway to the Stars - Palomar Mountains, 1948 July 14; F7938
    - Fishing Boats and Nets - San Pedro, 1949 March; F8291
    - Carlsbad Hotel: back patio..., ca. 1940s
    - Mt. San Gorgonio and dunes..., ca. 1940s
  - Frasher, Burton: Photographs of the High Sierras. v.p. (California) *, c.1927.; 56 original photographs. 18 x 43 cm. (Box 2)
    A collection of panoramic views copyrighted by Frashers of Pomonoa, showing mountain scenes in Mono, Inyo, and Kern Counties.
  - Frisch, A.: Photographs of Amazon Indians, Brazil., ca. 1867.; 10 prints. 24 x 19 cm., on sheet 42 x 32 cm. (Box 131)
  - Gabriel, Charles L., 18 items. Photographs. (Box 61)
  - Garnett, William A., 3 photographs. (Box 3)
  - Genthe, Arnold: Ezra Pound. [n.p. *, 193-?].; 1 item. 31.5 x 26cm. Original photograph.; Mounted without margins. (Box 16)
  - Genthe, Arnold: Kathleen Norris. New York.*, 1 item. 30 x 25.5cm. Original photograph. Mounted, 42 x 35 cm. (Box 16)
  - Genthe, Arnold: Mabel Ballin. New York, [ca. 1920].; 1 item. 15.5 x 10.5cm. Original photograph. (Box 16)
    Removed from the Hugo Ballin Collection.
  - Gibson, Ralph: Artifacts [pictures]. - New York: DEP Editions,**, [1985?]; 1 portfolio: photographs, b & w; 55.5 x 44cm. 10 images, either 35 x 27.5 cm. or 27.5 x 35 cm. Mounted and overmatted to 50.5 x 40.5 cm. or 40.5 x 50.5 cm. (Othertype Portfolio #9.)
    - Silhouette, Paris, 1982
    - Architectural Detail, New York, 1980
    - Window Washer, Paris, 1975
    - Street Artist, New York, 1981
    - Painter, London, 1984
    - Marcellus, Louvre, Paris, 1984
    - Waiter, Isle of Capri, 1983
    - Doorknob, New York, 1975
    - Architectural Detail, Rome, 1984
    - Antiquities Dealer, Rome, 1984
  - Gibson, Ralph: Deja-vu. New York (N.Y.), DEP Editions, ***, [ca.1973]; 1 item. 42.8 x 54.2 cm. Portfolio of photographs. 11 black and white images, either 35 x 27.5 cm. or 27.5 x 35 cm. Mounted and overmatted to 50.5 x 40.5 cm. or 40.5 x 50.5 cm.
    #24 of an edition of 25.
    Photographs from Deja-vu (New York, Lustrum Press, ca.1973) the second book in the Black Trilogy: Somnambulist (1970), Deja-vu (1973), Days at sea (1974). All photographs are signed, dated, and numbered on the verso. All prints are 35 x 27.5 cm., mounted and overmatted 50.5 x 40.5 cm., unless otherwise noted.
    - Girl holding glasses, 1971
    - Englishman, Derby, 1972
    - Cloud, New Mexico, 1972; Unmounted 27.5 x 35 cm., mounted 40.5 x 50.5 cm.
    - Crew cut man, San Francisco
    - House, Los Angeles, 1972
    - Doorways, Mexico, 1972
    - Sailor, 1972
    - Hand/Piano, 1973
    - Girl, door, sea, 1972
    - Arm, umbrella, sea, 1972
    - Man blowing nose, 1972
  - Gibson, Ralph: If & (silk). New York (N.Y.), DEP Editions, ***, [ca.1982]; 1 item. 42.5 x 54.3 cm. Portfolio of photographs. 15 black and white images, either 35.3 x 27.5 cm. or 27.5 x 35.3 cm. Mounted and overmatted to 40.5 x 50.6 cm. or 50.6 x 40.5 cm.
    #47 of an edition of 75.
    - Nude on grass, 1970
    - Mannequin in window, 1971
    - Woman with mask, 1972
    - Woman with statue, 1974
    - Woman's face with shadow, 1974
    - White nude--arms over head, 1974
    - Woman's hand on shoulder--brassiere, 1975
    - Woman's truncated profile, 1975
    - Frontal portrait--statue, 1976
    - Frontal portrait--derby, 1976
    - Detail of breast--arm, 1978
    - Portrait--woman--blonde curls, 1980
    - Woman in bridal gown, 1980
    - Woman on beach--Sardinia, 1980
    - Close up--white face, 1981
  - Goetz, Louis A.: The spirit of 1906. San Francisco., 1914.; 1 item. 23.5 x 18.5 cm. Unmounted photograph. (Box 62)
  - Good, Frank Mason*, 1 item. Photographs.
  - Graham, William M., 104 photographs. (Box 63)
  - Hammerschmidt, W. ***, 3 items. Photographs.
  - Hanna, Foreman ***, 2 items. Photographs.
    - "Morning Sky", ca. 1915; # 108; 10½ x 13½ ins. 26 x 34 cm.; Silver print, signed; mounted and overmatted: 40 x 48 cm.
    - Fresh Snow, ca. 1915; # 113; 10½ x 13½ ins. 27 x 34 cm.; Silver print, signed; mounted and overmatted: 26.5 x 34 cm.
  - Harding, Lonal V. (Box 121)
    1 portrait of Franklin D. Murphy.
  - Harris, Rodney G., 1 item. Photograph. (Box 64)
  - Haynes, Frank Jay: Collection of copy prints of views in Yellowstone and Yosemite. (Box 66)
  - Haynes, Willis P.: San Xavier del Bac interior. Tucson, Arizona. *, ca.189-.; 1 item. 25 x 20 cm. Photograph. Mounted, 35 x 27.5cm. (Box 22)
    View looking toward alter. Has been attributed to Carlton E. Watkins.
  - Heimann, Fritz, Photographs.
  - Hill, A. W. ***, 1 item. Photograph.
    - Wind Among the Firs, ca. 1930; # 43; 10 x 12 ins.: 28 x 32.5 cm.; photogravure print; signed; score lower right side; mounted: 50 x 40.3 cm.
  - Hillers, John K. *, 2 photographs. (Box 21)
  - Hills & Saunders, Photographers, 1 item. Photograph. (Box 65)
  - Holmes, Burton, 178 items. Photographs. (Box 67)
    Collection includes 161 glass slides of Latin America taken by Holmes for his travelogues.
  - Horst, Horst P.: Gertrude Stein. Paris (France)., 1946.; 1 item. 24.9 x 19.3 cm. Photograph. Mounted and overmatted 43 x 35.5 cm.; Fine gouge across Miss Stein's jacket.
  - ***Panorama do Rio de Janeiro., 18 x 118.5 cm. Stored flat in portfolio. Pasted on 45 x 147 cm. support board.
  - ***Photographers Collection., 1 item. Photograph.
  - Photographers Collection., 56 photographs. (Box 11)
  - Photographers Collection., 5 photographs. (Box 12)
  - Photographers Collection. (Box 122)
    23 photographs of the Grand Canyon, Colorado River and vicinity. 2 have Wharton's name on them, and the rest are attributed to him. All were done under the auspices of the C.C. Pierce Company.
  - *The Jewel of Asia, Ruth St. Denis. n.p., undated; 1 item. 34.5 x 27 cm. Photograph. Mounted 59 x 38.5cm. (Box 33)
  - **Photographers Collection., 1 item. Photograph.
  - Photographers Collection., 2 items. Photographs. (Box 68)
  - ***Photographers Collection., 7 items. Photographs.
  - *Photographs. Seattle., 1924.; 3 items. 35 x 28cm. Unmounted photographs. (Box 13)
    1. Fir timber along the Chuckanut Drive.
    2. North end Baker R. Canyon, Washington.
    3. A wall of trees - fir and cedar - Washington.
  - Portrait of André Kertész. New York., 1978.; 1 item. 35.3 27.6cm. Original photograph.
  - Photographers Collection., 1 item. Photograph. (Box 69)
  - ***Photographers Collection., 6 items. Photographs.
    - "The Wood Wind Choir, L.A. Lamb to Louis Flechenstein 1905", # 1122; 6 x 9¼ins: 15.3 x 23.4cm; Gum bichromate print; mounted and overmatted: 40.3 x 50.3 cm.
    - Self portrait, 1908; # 1115; 2½ x 2 ins: 9.8 x 7 cm.; Silver print; mounted and overmatted: 35.5 x 27.2 cm.
    - The Fifth of Beethoven C minor [Louis Albert Lamb to his friend, Louis Flechenstein], MCMV-AD; # 1113; 9¼ x 6¼ ins.: 23.7 x 16 cm.; Gum bichromate print; mounted and overmatted: 50.3 x 40.5 cm.
    - "To my friend, Louis Flechenstein", 1905; # 1121; 9 x 3¼ ins.: 32 x 7.9 cm.; Gum bichromate print; Munch marks from silverfish top left center and edge.; mounted and overmatted: 50.2 x 40.3 cm.
    - "A Theme for Oboes :Louis Albert Lamb to Louis Flechenstein", MCMV; # 1120; 3 x 5¼ ins.: 8 x 13.5 cm.; Gum bichromate print; mounted and overmatted: 50 x 40.5 cm.
    - "The Silvery Barge", ca. 1905; 8 x 4½ ins.: 19.5 x 13.5 cm.; Two color gum bichromate print; mounted and overmatted: 50.4 x 40.5 cm.
  - Capitol at Washinton, D.C. Langenheim's American Stereoscope Views, [ca. 1862].; 1 item. 8 x 17 cm. Stereograph. (Box 70)
    A view of the capitol building with the dome under construction.
  - *Photographers Collection., 6 photographs. (Box 9)
    - Victorian Still Life, Print. No. 1
      The Victorian bell jar (with artificial flowers) and ceramic figure were found in an old plantation house. Here they have much of the crispness and delicacy of some of the Dutch flower painters.
    - The Deathly Forest, Print. No. 2
      Something of the strange and disturbing quality of the south Louisiana landscape is here conveyed. A weird and crested form rises in the middle distance, while to the upper left is something suggesting a fantastic little creature escaped from a Bosch painting.
    - Three Vistas through One Wall, Print. No. 3
      Through the broken brick wall of an old industrial building we see three separate and distinct vistas - the mind expects some kind of connection in these vistas - but apparently there is none. Yet the picture is not a collage. The feeling of different kinds of space here releases the true magic of the object.
    - The Head in the Wall, Print. No. 4
      Here, by a process of natural magic, a broken opening in a shattered building become the very avatar of war, the head of havoc itself, brooding over the ruin which faces a society which cannot control its own destructive forces.
    - The Moss Weeps (Woodland Plantation), Print. No. 5
      For further information on this house, see photographers' book, Ghosts Along the Mississippi (Plates 93-99).
    - Corroded Angels, 1949; Print. No. 6
      Photograph of Louisiana Country Cemetery.
  - Photographers Collection., 1 photograph.
  - Photographers Collection., 2 items. Photographs. (Box 71)
  - Photographers Collection., 19 items. Photographs. (Box 72)
  - Photographers Collection., 4 items. Photographs.
  - Photographers Collection., 13 items. Photographs. (Box 73)
  - Photographs of the Southewest. v.p., 189-.; 144 items. Cyanotypes. (Box 112)
    The collection includes portraits of Indians, views of New Mexican towns and ruins, and portraits of Lummis and his family.
  - *Gertrude Stein. n.p., ca. 1932.; 1 item. 19 x 21cm. Photograph. (Box 10)
    Profile portrait of Gertrude Stein taken against a background of a distant valley.
  - *Photographers Collection., 1 item. 36 x 46 cm. Photograph. (Box 7)
    Penciled note on back: "Taken about April 1947 ... the last picture taken of Ernest Dawson."
  - *Photographers Collection., 2 items. Photographs. (Box 19)
    Composite photographs of Black children. Knoxville (Tenn.), McCrary & Branson, 1897.
    1. 9 Black babies, 16.5 x 52 cm., "Alligator Bait."
    2. 14 Black children, 11 x 43 cm., "All coons look alike ..."
  - Photographers Collection., 24 items. Photographs.
    20 items - box 74.
  - *Edward Sherriff Curtis. Los Angeles., ca. 1950.; 1 item. 24 x 19cm. Photograph.
    Mr. Magnuson is Curtis's son-in-law.
  - **Photographers Collection., 2 items. Photographs.
  - Photographers Collection., Photographs. (Box 75)
    1 photograph of Henry Miller with Brenda Venus.
  - Photographers Collection., 5 items. 16.5 x 11.5 cm. Photographs. (Box 76)
    Taken on Long Island Sound in the summer of 1934 when Einstein was staying at Watch Hill. Erich Marx was related to Albert Einstein through his grandmother.
  - ***Photographers Collection., 2 items. Photographs.
  - Photographers Collection., 1 item. Photograph. (Box 77)
  - Barbara Morgan. Los Angeles., 1972.; 1 item. 25.5 x 20.5 cm. Photograph. (Box 78)
    Taken on the occasion of a dinner party at the home of Annita Delano, July 1972.
  - **Photographers Collection., 1 item. Photograph. (Box 18)
    - [untitled.], # 187; 7½ x 11 ins.; 19 x 27.5 cm.; A Pure Gold and Silver print (patented); foxing overall
  - ***Photographers Collection., 18 photographs.
    - Dr. Daisetz Suzuki
    - Martha Graham in "Letter to the world," (seated on bench), 1940
    - Martha Graham in "Letter to the world," (with skirt making arc), 1940
    - Dr. Daisetz Suzuki (in study)
    - Gerald Heard, 1950
    - Professor Joseph Campbell and Student, Sarah Lawrence College, 195-
    - Resurrection in the junkyard, 1947
    - Charles Sheeler and his favorite beech tree, 1945
    - Walnut, 1943
    - Willard Morgan tossing cats, 1942
    - Girl playing recorder (from Summers Children), 1951
    - Lloyd's head, 1951?
    - Valerie Betts in "Desperate heart"
    - Ikon in time, 1964; (photo mantage)
    - Charles Weidman in "Lynchtown", 1938
    - José Limon, Peon, from "Mexican Suite", 1944
    - Fossil in formation, 1965
    - Artificial life from the laboratory, 1967
    - Beech Tree I, 1945
  - ***Barbara Morgan Exhibition Collection. v.p., v.d.; 144 items. Mounted salon print photographs. (Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130)
    - Jose Limon, Chaconne, 1944; Print: 19? x 14?; Mount: 28 x 22
    - Martha Graham, Letter to the World, 1940; Print: 14½ x 19½; Mount: 28 x 22
      (Duet with Merce Cunningham "Dear March Come In")
    - Artificial Life from the Laboratory, 1967; Photomontage; Print: 13½ x 14?; Mount: 27? x 22
    - Valerie Bettis, Desperate Heart, 1944; Photomontage II; Print: 19 x 14?; Mount: 28 x 22
    - Valerie Bettis, Desperate Heart (Kick), 1944; Print: 19½ x 15?; Mount: 28 x 22
    - Beech Tree I, 1945; Print: 18 x 13½; Mount: 27? x 21
    - Merce Cunningham, Totem Ancestor, 1942; Print: 19 x 14¼; Mount: 27 x 21
    - Martha Graham, Letter to the World (Finale), 1940; Print: 19 x 14½; Mount: 27 x 22
    - Martha Graham, Frontier (Fear), 1935; Print: 13½ x 18¾; Mount: 21 x 27
    - Martha Graham, American Document, 1938; Print: 18 x 15¼; Mount: 27 x 22
      (Duet with Erick Hawkins "Puritan Love Duet")
    - Martha Graham, Celebration (Trio), 1937; Print: 19 x 15; Mount: 27 x 22
    - Leaf Adrift in City, 1970; Photomontage; Print: 18 x 14½; Mount: 27 x 21
    - Emanation I, 1940; Light Drawing; Print: 17¼; x 13½; Mount: 26 x 21
    - Martha Graham, Letter to the World (Swirl), 1940; Print: 15 x 18?; Mount: 22 x 26
    - Merce Cunningham, Root of the Unfocus, 1942; Photomontage; Print: 13½ x 18; Mount: 20 x 26
    - Doris Humphrey, Shakers, 1938; Print: 15 x 18?; Mount: 22 x 26
      (Bea Seckler Solo)
    - Stone Fence, 1946; Print: 18¾ x 12¾; Mount: 26 x 20
    - Martha Graham, El Penitente, 1940; Print: 18 x 14½; Mount: 26 x 21
      (Merce Cunningham Solo "Christus"
    - Merce Cunningham, Leap, 1942; Print: 18½ x 13?; Mount: 26 x 21
    - Chassis-Cranium, 1947; Print: 17½ x 14¼; Mount: 25 x 21
    - Cadenza, 1940; Light Drawing; Print: 17¾ x 14¼; Mount: 25 x 22
    - Use Litter Basket, 1943; Photomontage; Print: 14½ x 17¼; Mount: 22 x 25
    - Jose Limon, Mexican Suite, 1944; Print: 16? x 14¼; Mount: 25 x 21
      (Jose Limon and May O'Donnell Duet "Conquistador)
    - Martha Graham, Extasis, 1935; Print: 18? x 14½; Mount: 25 x 21
    - Jose Limon, Mexican Suite ("Indian"), 1944; Print: 17¾ x 14?; Mount: 25 x 21
    - Mid-Summer Solstice, 1940; Light Drawing; Print: 15 x 17?; Mount: 22 x 25
    - Charles Weidman, Lynchtown (Group), 1938; Print: 12? x 19; Mount: 18 x 25
    - Battered Tin Can, 1942; Print: 12 x 17; Mount: 19 x 25
    - Martha Graham, El Penitente, 1940; Print: 17 x 12½; Mount: 25 x 20
      (Erick Hawkins Solo "El Flagellante")
    - Beaumont Newhall, Ansel Adams and Willard Morgan (in Morgan's studio), 1942; Print: 14? x 17¾; Mount: 22 x 25
    - Beech Tree XIV, 1945; Print: 13¼ x 14¾; Mount: 22 x 21
    - Beaumont Newhall and ansel Adams Jumping, 1942; Print: 14½ x 14½; Mount: 22 x 21
    - Charles Weidman, Lynchtown, 1933; Print: 14¾ x 14?; Mount: 21 x 22
    - Beech Limb, 1945; Print: 15 x 15; Mount: 22 x 21
    - Funkia Leaf, 1950; Solarized; Print: 13? x 11; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Martha Graham, Satyric Festival, 1958; Print: 12? x 9¼; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Dr. Daisetz Teitaro Suzuki at Work, 1958; Print: 12? x 9¼; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Martha Graham, Primitive Mysteries (Group), 1958; Print: 10? x 10½; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Tossed Cats, 1942; Print: 10? x 13½; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Broken Light Bulb, 1945; Print: 13? x 9½; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Charles Weidman, Daddy Was A Fireman, 1944; Print: 13¼ x 10½; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Ice on Window II, 1942; Print: 13¾ x 9¾; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Corn Stalk, 1944-1971; Solarized; Print: 13½ x 10; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Hearst Over The People, 1939; Print: 13? x 10?; Mount: 19? x 15 ?
    - Man's Knee, 1940; Print: 12¾ x 10; Mount: 20 x 11
    - Fossil In Formation, 1965; Photomontage; Print: 11 3/16 x 12; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Stump, 1945; Print: 9½ x 12?; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Doug In Rafters, Camp Treetops, 1943; Print: 13½ x 10½; Mount: 19 x 16
    - Asadata Dafora (Sierra Leone, Africa), 1942; Print: 13½ x 10¾; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Brainwashed, 1966-1969; Photomontage; Print: 13 x 9¾; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Martha Graham, Frontier (Fence), 1935; Print: 10? x 13½; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Martha Graham, Every Soul Is A Circus, 1940; Print: 13? x 10; Mount: 20 x 16
      (Duet with Erick Hawkins)
    - Ice On Window, 1942; Print: 13? x 10¼; Mount: 20 x 16
    - Macy's Window (Reflections), ca. 1940; Print: 11¼ x 16; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Resurrection in the Junkyard, 1947; Print: 10¼ x 13?; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Forming Currents, 1970; Print: 10? x 13?; Mount: 16 x 20
    - Willard Morgan with Model A Leica, Bandelier National Monument, 1928; Print: 12¾ x 9?; Mount: 19 x 16
    - Caterpillar Beech, 1945; Print: 10? x 10?; Mount: 16 x 16
    - Auto Crash, 1947; Print: 11? x 10; Mount: 19 x 16
    - Planet On Fire, 1971 Photomontage; Print: 11? x 10; Mount: 20 x 14
    - Boy and Goat, 1940; Print: 10? x 11?; Mount: 14 x 16
    - Beech Tree VI, 1945; Print: 12¾ x 9¼; Mount: 18 x 14
    - Charles Sheeler and His Favorite Beech Tree, 1945; Print: 12½ x 10?; Mount: 18 x 14
    - Dawn Window, 1945; Print: 7? x 13?; Mount: 14 x 19
    - Bee Sting, 1948; Print: 10 x 12?; Mount: 15 x 18
    - Ghost of the Crash, 1947; Print: 11¼ x 10?; Mount: 18 x 16
    - Out To Pasture, Camp Treetops, 1946; Print: 9 x 12?; Mount: 16 x 18
    - Ice On Window, Santa, 1942; Print: 9? x 11?; Mount: 16 x 17¾
    - Doris Humphrey, Passacaglia, 1938; Print: 10? x 12?; Mount: 16 x 17
    - Spring on Madison Square, 1938; Photomontage; Print: 13? x 16?; Mount: 20 x 23
    - Ikons in Time-Stream, 1963; Print: 13 x 17½; Mount: 19 x 25
    - Begonia, 1943; Macro; Print: 12 x 16?; Mount: 19 x 23
    - Orbiting, 1940; Ligh Drawing; Print: 18? x 12; Mount: 26 x 19
    - Jose Limon, Mexican Suite ("Peon"), 1944; Print: 12 x 16¾; Mount: 18 x 24
    - Pregnant, 1940; Print: 16¼ x 12?; Mount: 24 x 19
    - Solstice (Ice on Window Series), 1942; Print: 16½ x 11¼; Mount: 24 x 18
    - Trajectory, 1946; Print: 17½ x 12; Mount: 24 x 17
    - Bedtime Story, Camp Treetops, 1947; Print: 17½ x 13?; Mount: 20 x 24
    - Doris Humphrey, With My Red Fires ("Matriarch"), 1938; Print: 13½ x 15¾; Mount: 20 x 23
    - Corn Stalk, 1944; Print: 14? x 11¼; Mount: 22 x 18
    - Ansel Adams Jumping On Stool (In Barbara Morgan's Studio), 1942; Print: 13? x ?; Mount: 18 x 21
    - Beech Tree II, 1945; Print: 11? x 16½; Mount: 18 x 23
    - Delicate Beech, 1945; Print: 14? x 13?; Mount: 23 x 20
    - Briarlock, 1943; Photomontage; Print: 13? x 13?; Mount: 21 x 19
    - Martha Graham, American Document, 1938; Print: 11? x 14½; Mount: 18? x 22
    - Children Dancing By Lake, Camp Treetops, 1940; Print: 11¼ x 16; Mount: 17 x 21
    - Lloyd's Head, 1944; Print: 15¼ x 10?; Mount: 22 x 17
    - Martha Graham, Frontier (Running), 1935; Print: 10? x 13?; Mount: 17 x 20
    - Cradled, 1940; Print: 13? x 10?; Mount: 21 x 16
    - Fossil In Formation, 1965; Photomontage; Print: 12½ x 16?; Mount: 19 x 23